{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Window Air Conditioner Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/40291/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40291,"taskName":"Window A/C Unit - Service or Relocate","taskDescription":"Relocate or Service a Window Air Conditioning Unit","xmTaskDescriptor":"Window Air Conditioner Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":370,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Airconditioning Window A/C Condition system","textMessagingName":"Repr Window A/C","rolloverLongDesc":"Includes taking units down or covering them up for the winter \u0026 remounting or uncovering them in the spring.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes thru-wall units.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Relocate or Service a Window Air Conditioning Unit.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Window AC Repair Service \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Move Window AC Unit","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":39,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Window A/C Service","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Window A/C Unit - Service or Relocate","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Window A/C Unit Project","urlName":"Window-A-C-Unit-Service-or-Relocate","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Window AC Repair Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"Airconditioning,Window,A/C,Condition,system,airconditioners,coolers,systems,conditioner,move,units,hvac,heating,cooling,coolair,conditioning,ac,Air,Relocate,Unit","emcCategoryOid":-12002,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":396,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40291/":{"taskOID":40291,"originalTaskOID":40291,"setID":396,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1418,"questionDisplayText":"Problem description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes the nature of the problem?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6602,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Unit not running","answerDisplayText":"Unit not running","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4196,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No air conditioning in one location","answerDisplayText":"No air conditioning in one location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4195,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"No air conditioning in all locations","answerDisplayText":"No air conditioning in all locations","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4286,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Not enough cooling in one location","answerDisplayText":"Not enough cooling in one location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4285,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Not enough cooling anywhere","answerDisplayText":"Not enough cooling anywhere","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3504,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Leaking","answerDisplayText":"Leaking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":782,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Annual maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Annual maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204392,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Inefficient HVAC","answerDisplayText":"Inefficient HVAC","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6936,"questionDisplayText":"Equipment Age","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How old is your current air conditioning system? (in years)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10097,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 5 years","answerDisplayText":"Less than 5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10098,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"5 - 10 years","answerDisplayText":"5 - 10 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10099,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"11 - 15 years","answerDisplayText":"11 - 15 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10100,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"16 - 20 years","answerDisplayText":"16 - 20 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10101,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 20 years","answerDisplayText":"More than 20 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203064,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Looking for Parts Only","answerDisplayText":"Looking for Parts Only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1418,"questionDisplayText":"Problem description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes the nature of the problem?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6602,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Unit not running","answerDisplayText":"Unit not running","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4196,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No air conditioning in one location","answerDisplayText":"No air conditioning in one location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4195,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"No air conditioning in all locations","answerDisplayText":"No air conditioning in all locations","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4286,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Not enough cooling in one location","answerDisplayText":"Not enough cooling in one location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4285,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Not enough cooling anywhere","answerDisplayText":"Not enough cooling anywhere","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3504,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Leaking","answerDisplayText":"Leaking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":782,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Annual maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Annual maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204392,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Inefficient HVAC","answerDisplayText":"Inefficient HVAC","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6602,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Unit not running","answerDisplayText":"Unit not running","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4196,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No air conditioning in one location","answerDisplayText":"No air conditioning in one location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4195,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"No air conditioning in all locations","answerDisplayText":"No air conditioning in all locations","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4286,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Not enough cooling in one location","answerDisplayText":"Not enough cooling in one location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4285,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Not enough cooling anywhere","answerDisplayText":"Not enough cooling anywhere","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3504,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Leaking","answerDisplayText":"Leaking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":782,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Annual maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Annual maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204392,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Inefficient HVAC","answerDisplayText":"Inefficient HVAC","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6936,"questionDisplayText":"Equipment Age","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How old is your current air conditioning system? (in years)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10097,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 5 years","answerDisplayText":"Less than 5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10098,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"5 - 10 years","answerDisplayText":"5 - 10 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10099,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"11 - 15 years","answerDisplayText":"11 - 15 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10100,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"16 - 20 years","answerDisplayText":"16 - 20 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10101,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 20 years","answerDisplayText":"More than 20 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10097,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 5 years","answerDisplayText":"Less than 5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10098,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"5 - 10 years","answerDisplayText":"5 - 10 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10099,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"11 - 15 years","answerDisplayText":"11 - 15 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10100,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"16 - 20 years","answerDisplayText":"16 - 20 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10101,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 20 years","answerDisplayText":"More than 20 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203064,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Looking for Parts Only","answerDisplayText":"Looking for Parts Only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203064,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Looking for Parts Only","answerDisplayText":"Looking for Parts Only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}